NELSON DALY nelson.daly@outlook.com | nelsond.tech

About Me

An inquisitive and proactive Front-End Developer, with strong problem-solving skills and experience delivering results in a fast-paced environment. Able to communicate effectively with all levels of seniority and degrees of technical understanding.

Skills

TypeScript / JavaScript | Angular 13 | HTML5 | CSS3 | Object-Oriented Programming | Java 8 | C#

Demonstrable Experience

Portfolio Web App (nelsond.tech/this.app)

• Built a Single-Page Application in the style of a code editor, using Angular 13 and TypeScript, with a resizable preview section showcasing live demonstrations of the following additional projects created.

Issue Tracker App (<u>nelsond.tech/issuetracker.app</u>)

• Designed and developed an embedded CRUD web application, featuring vanilla TypeScript chart visualizations.

Scientific Calculator App (nelsond.tech/scicalculator.app)

• Created an emulation of Casio fx-991MS. Implemented 80% functionality for the minimum viable product.

Local Weather Forecast App (nelsond.tech/localweather.app)

• Built a live weather forecast widget, consuming JSON data from a third-party REST API / microservice.

Career History

Enprod

Technical Consultant

2021 – Present

• Producing varying technical solutions to help clients optimise operations and efficiently achieve objectives.

Goldman Sachs

Support – Engineering Division

2013 - 2021

• Provided support to cross-region Engineering teams, across multiple Business Units, for numerous management systems. Developed Confluence, SharePoint and internal websites. Analyzed data and distributed weekly reports.

Education

University of Pennsylvania • Certificate in SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript 2020 – 2021
• Certificate in SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript
• Certificate in SD2x: Data Structures and Software Design
• Certificate in SD1x: Software Development Fundamentals
Microsoft • Certificate in DEV262x: Logic and Computational Thinking
• <u>Certificate</u> in DAT201x: Querying Data with Transact-SQL
Chartered Institute for Securities & Investment (CISI) • Level 3 Award for Introduction to Securities and Investment

British Academy of New Music

2011 - 2013

• Level 3 RSL Extended Diploma for Music Technology